(Raj:)You have no idea. They're everywhere.
(Howard:)Okay, guys, think.
How do we keep Raj in the country?
PENNY [FROM OUTSIDE]:
Why doesn't he just get another job?
(Howard(after Raj whispers to him):)What are you asking me for?
I don't know if you can talk now or not.
(Raj:)Oh, beef.
I'm gonna miss you so much.
Did you know at the Mumbai McDonald's,
you can't get a Big Mac?
(Raj:)All you can get
is a Chicken Maharaja Mac.
And the special sauce?
(Raj:)Curry. Which in India,
believe you me, is really not that special.
(Leonard:)-Don't worry. You'll find another job.
-Yeah, let me start practicing for it.
"Do you want fries
with that Maharaja Mac?"
(Sheldon:)Hi, Leonard. Hello, Raj.
(Raj:)Hello, Sheldon.
(Sheldon:)Forgive me.
I'm not adept at reading facial cues.